jigsawacademy.com 2018-10-09

# Privacy Policy of Jigsaw Academy

#### Overview

  * ‘Jigsaw Academy’ respects its user’s privacy and recognizes the need to protect any personal information you share with us. We would like to assure you that we follow appropriate standards when it comes to protecting your privacy on our website.
  * This Privacy Policy applies to your use of any of our websites, products or services, and any interaction we may have with you at any time by telephone, email or any other means.
  * No system is 100% secure so we do not claim to comply exactly per the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679, but we take serious measures to protect your data as much as possible.
  * We take your privacy seriously and are committed to protecting your right to privacy as a user of our website. We have made every effort to ensure your information is secure. This privacy policy information covers what information is collected, what we do with it, and what you can do about it. You can use this information to make your decisions about your privacy.
  * BY USING OUR SERVICES OR BY OTHERWISE GIVING US YOUR INFORMATION, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. Please review the following carefully so that you understand our privacy practices.

#### About us and the website

  * ‘Jigsaw Academy’ provides instructor-led, classroom and online training for analytics, big data and related technologies. Our courses are designed to help participants get hands on training in analytics and related technologies.

#### ‘Jigsaw Academy’ Information Practices

  * Every effort has been taken to ensure the accuracy of the information on the website; however the content is subject to change. We are not responsible for any damages arising from the use of the information held on this server. We assure that all our downloadable training content is virus free. However, ‘Jigsaw Academy’ can accept no liability for damages resulting from virus infection.

#### Information collected by ‘Jigsaw Academy’

  * You have total control on the privacy of your information. Your information will never be sold, exchanged or disclosed to any third party for marketing purposes. You can opt to receive offers from us. You can browse our website without registration. We may collect and store the information that you voluntarily disclose to us, in order to access our free tests and discussion forum. We do not share your personal information with any third party. We do not collect information about our visitors from email databases, private/ public organization or bodies.
  * Our website may automatically record information that your browser sends to our webserver. This information may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  * We may use your information to contact you via email or telephone, typically to get feedback, to inform you about new products or provide support on your issues. If you do not want us to contact you via email, you can unsubscribe at any time. All the email communications may not be encrypted or secure.
  * When you purchase our online products or register for a classroom training, you need to make the payment online, thus you will be required to share with us your personal information such as name, e-mail address, telephone number, address(s), credit card number, expiration, and CVV number. During this program, we store your contact information in our registration and order-entry systems. Your credit card information is never stored in our system as it is processed by our payment gateway which uses Secure Encryption Technology, SSL. Our payment processing partners are PayPal, Razorpay and EBS.
  * We keep your information while you are registered with us or license our software so that we are able to provide the service to you but we also keep it after you’ve left us, though only for as long as we need it. How long we keep it depends very much on the type of information we are holding and the purpose for which we need it. We also take into account our legal obligations in respect of how long we keep your data.
  * Protecting the online privacy of children is vital. If you are under 18 years old, please do not provide us with your name, contact details or any other information about yourself.

#### Cookie Information

  * In order to enhance your online experience and track website performance, our website uses cookies. They do not give us any personal information.

#### E-commerce tracking

  * To provide a superior online shopping experience, we may use cookies to temporarily store names and email addresses. Cookies will never store credit card information as they’re processed using payment gateways that use Secure Encryption Technology.

#### External Links

  * Our website may have links to other sites, which include third party websites or resources. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and information practices of third party websites. Please read the privacy policies of third party websites as every website has different terms of use and privacy policies.

#### Course Content

  * Course content for all the study programs both online and blended programs, is provided only for the purpose of education and guidance. The course content is reviewed regularly and is subject to change without notice. ‘Jigsaw Academy’ reserves the right to modify training content without notice.

#### Copyright information

  * You can electronically copy or take print outs of the website pages, only for personal use. ‘Jigsaw Academy’ holds the copyright to all the material on this website, unless otherwise indicated. A written permission from the copyright holder must be obtained for any use of this material other than for purposes permitted by law.

#### Personal Information Policy Image and Video Capture

  * Any images captured during events organized and hosted by ‘Jigsaw Academy’ should not be misused. That includes pictures of ‘Jigsaw Academy’ staff and training participants. If you enroll in a Jigsaw Academy™ course your picture may also be featured in photos or videos of the Jigsaw Academy™ classes. You can contact us if you do not wish the same. Please send us an email at info@jigsawacademy.com
  * Telephonic Conversations: We may record inbound and outbound calls for quality control and training purposes. We never share this with external parties.
  * Sharing your personal information: If you have purchased a Jigsaw Academy™ course, we may ask you for a testimonial and with your authorization, display your testimonial, photos or videos on our website or in our social media channels such as Facebook, YouTube, Flickr etc. You should be aware that your publicly identifiable information could be used to send you promotional, unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for your personal information which you have chosen to display. If you do not want us to feature your pictures/testimonials on our website or on our social media channels, you can send an email to info@jigsawacademy.com

#### Personal Information Corrections

  * You can contact us if you notice that the information we are holding is incorrect or incomplete. Please send us an email at info@jigsawacademy.com

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

  * These privacy policy terms may change time to time and we reserve the right to change the terms of the privacy policy at any time as legislation and business practices change. We are not under any obligation to explicitly inform all users of these changes. Hence, kindly visit these policies on our website from time to time.

#### Deleting Personal Information

  * If you would like to delete your information from our servers, write to info@jigsawacademy.com

#### Privacy Policy Questions?

  * If you have any questions regarding Jigsaw Academy™’s Privacy Policy, please write to info@jigsawacademy.com
